

# **MARTIN Claire**

## Student in Networks and Telecommunications Apprentice software developer

I'm interested in computer science, and will be able to make myself useful by using the programming and project management skills I've acquired in my further training, and my experience as a software developer.

## Personal information

Nationality: French

Date of birth: 13th of February 2002 Place of birth : Grasse, FRANCE

## Contact



98, chemin des Oliviers, 06460 Saint-Vallier-de-Thiey, FRANCE



+33 7 81 67 39 58



claire.martin8@etu.univ-cotedazur.fr



https://eclaizr.github.io/claire-martinportfolio/accueil.html

## Langages

French Mother tongue, C2 level

English 👍 💠 💠 Upper Intermediate, B2 level

German 👃 👃 📥 Elementary, A2 level

# Skills

## **Technical**

Programming langages: C, Python, Java Web development: HTML, CSS, PHP Database management: MySQL

Operating Systems: Linux, Unix, Windows Configuring Cisco network equipements: routers, switchs, firewalls

Simulating a network: cisco packet tracer,

Communication and project management: Gantt Chart, Risk Analysis, RACI

#### **Personal**

Teamwork | Autonomous | curious | creative

## Interests

- Computer sciences
- Arduino
- Art
- Astonomy
- Nature

## Education

## University Institure of Technology - Sophia Antipolis - FRANCE

Bachelor Universitaire de Technologie in Networks and Telecommunications.

2022 - Now

Equivalent to a three-year intensive course in networks, telecommunications, computer sciences and cybersecurity.

Including a sandwich course at Ineo Defense as a software developer.

#### ISEN Yncréa - Toulon - FRANCE

2020 - 2022

Equivalent to a two-year intensive course in mathematics, physics and engineering sciences.

## **Amiral de Grasse Highschool - Grasse - FRANCE**

Baccalaureat S/SVT with honours - equivalent to A Levels in maths, Physics, Electronics, Chemestry, Biology

2017 - 2020

Mathematics speciality, arts option.

I took the Information and Digital Creation option, which led me to conceive a chameleon robot for the baccalaureate exams and obtained the highest

# **Professional experience**

#### Sandwich course in software development at INEO DEFENSE Valbonne - FRANCE

September 2023 - Now

My missions involve studying and implementing solutions for the security of the company's software and projects.

#### Study Project for Thalès Alenia Space - Sophia Antipolis - FRANCE

November 2023 - June 2023

- Recovered, analyzed and filtered a frame data from a raw binary file.
- Created and managed a database, a PHPMyAdmin server and Apache2 server to host the website on a Raspberry Pi 3.
- Wrote PHP requests and displayed the requested data on the website.

# Additional Informations

- French spelling Diploma: Certificat Volaire
- Deutsches Sprachdiplom A2 level

